Just respecting his choice
We have nothing against you
It's just that for the Fu family all these years
finding Chenzhou wasn't easy
Now that his status has changed
we naturally have to be cautious about many things
Are you saying
before Fu Chenzhou's identity was confirmed
marrying him was impulsive
and now that his identity is confirmed
if I continue to stand
by his side I'm just taking advantage
Mingyao you misunderstood
we didn't mean that
That's good
We all just care about Chenzhou
I understand you care about him
but caring about him doesn't mean you should
doubt his choices first
Second Granduncle
when I was in a tough spot she was
the only one who firmly chose me
If the Fu family acknowledges me
you should acknowledge my choice first
Ah